var words = 
[
    {
        "question": "ائْتِيَا",
        "answer": "Come both of you",
        "pcklId": "227",
        "tlit": "i'tiyā",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَتَيْنَا",
        "answer": "We come",
        "pcklId": "228",
        "tlit": "ataynā",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْتِي",
        "answer": "comes",
        "pcklId": "229",
        "tlit": "yatī",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْتِيهِ",
        "answer": "comes to it",
        "pcklId": "230",
        "tlit": "yatīhi",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْتُونَ",
        "answer": "give",
        "pcklId": "490",
        "tlit": "yu'tūna",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "آتَيْنَا",
        "answer": "We gave",
        "pcklId": "491",
        "tlit": "ātaynā",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجْرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a reward",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "ajrun",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَخَذَتْهُمْ",
        "answer": "so seized them",
        "pcklId": "109",
        "tlit": "fa-akhadhathum",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْآخِرَةِ",
        "answer": "in the Hereafter",
        "pcklId": "132",
        "tlit": "bil-ākhirati",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Hereafter",
        "pcklId": "133",
        "tlit": "l-ākhirati",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرَةِ",
        "answer": "the Hereafter",
        "pcklId": "134",
        "tlit": "l-ākhirati",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "When",
        "pcklId": "209",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "281",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَإِذَا",
        "answer": "then behold",
        "pcklId": "282",
        "tlit": "fa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَإِذَا",
        "answer": "but when",
        "pcklId": "283",
        "tlit": "fa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "284",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "but when",
        "pcklId": "285",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "آذَنَّاكَ",
        "answer": "We announce (to) You",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "ādhannāka",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "آذَانِنَا",
        "answer": "our ears",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "ādhāninā",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "آذَانِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their ears",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "ādhānihim",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضَ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "359",
        "tlit": "l-arḍa",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِلْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "and to the earth",
        "pcklId": "360",
        "tlit": "walil'arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the land",
        "pcklId": "361",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضَ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "362",
        "tlit": "l-arḍa",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآفَاقِ",
        "answer": "the horizons",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "l-āfāqi",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "463",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "464",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "465",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "466",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "467",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "Those who",
        "pcklId": "1123",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "1124",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالَّذِي",
        "answer": "in the One Who",
        "pcklId": "1125",
        "tlit": "bi-alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "the One Who",
        "pcklId": "1126",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "1127",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "the One Who",
        "pcklId": "1128",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "which",
        "pcklId": "1129",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "1130",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "1131",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "(of) what",
        "pcklId": "1132",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "1133",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّذَيْنِ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "1134",
        "tlit": "alladhayni",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "1135",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّتِي",
        "answer": "which",
        "pcklId": "1136",
        "tlit": "allatī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالَّتِي",
        "answer": "by (that) which",
        "pcklId": "1137",
        "tlit": "bi-allatī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "One who",
        "pcklId": "1138",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "(to) those who",
        "pcklId": "1139",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "the One Who",
        "pcklId": "1140",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "then those who",
        "pcklId": "1141",
        "tlit": "fa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "the One Who",
        "pcklId": "1142",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "1143",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "1144",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "for those who",
        "pcklId": "1145",
        "tlit": "lilladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "And those who",
        "pcklId": "1146",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "1147",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلِيمٍ",
        "answer": "painful",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "alīmin",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَٰهُكُمْ",
        "answer": "your god",
        "pcklId": "127",
        "tlit": "ilāhukum",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَٰهٌ",
        "answer": "(is) God",
        "pcklId": "128",
        "tlit": "ilāhun",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2376",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2377",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2378",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah made us speak",
        "pcklId": "2379",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2380",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah ",
        "pcklId": "2381",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(is) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2382",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2383",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "in Allah",
        "pcklId": "2384",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّهِ",
        "answer": "to Allah",
        "pcklId": "2385",
        "tlit": "lillahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2386",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْهِ",
        "answer": "to it",
        "pcklId": "599",
        "tlit": "ilayhi",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيَّ",
        "answer": "to me",
        "pcklId": "600",
        "tlit": "ilayya",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْهِ",
        "answer": "to Him",
        "pcklId": "601",
        "tlit": "ilayhi",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "towards",
        "pcklId": "602",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "603",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِلَيْهِ",
        "answer": "and to Him",
        "pcklId": "604",
        "tlit": "wa-ilayhi",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "605",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْهِ",
        "answer": "To Him",
        "pcklId": "606",
        "tlit": "ilayhi",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "607",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْ",
        "answer": "or",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "am",
        "frequency": "137",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْرَهَا",
        "answer": "its affair",
        "pcklId": "209",
        "tlit": "amrahā",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُمَمٍ",
        "answer": "nations",
        "pcklId": "110",
        "tlit": "umamin",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَمَّا",
        "answer": "Then as for",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "fa-ammā",
        "frequency": "55",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَمَّا",
        "answer": "And as for",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "wa-ammā",
        "frequency": "55",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِمَّا",
        "answer": "And if",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "wa-immā",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "446",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believed",
        "pcklId": "447",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "448",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "449",
        "tlit": "yu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمِنًا",
        "answer": "secure",
        "pcklId": "589",
        "tlit": "āminan",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُنْثَىٰ",
        "answer": "female",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "unthā",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْإِنْسِ",
        "answer": "and the men",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "wal-insi",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْإِنْسِ",
        "answer": "and the men",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "wal-insi",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْإِنْسَانُ",
        "answer": "man",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "l-insānu",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْإِنْسَانِ",
        "answer": "man",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "l-insāni",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوَّلَ",
        "answer": "(the) first",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "awwala",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَاتُهُ",
        "answer": "its Verses",
        "pcklId": "329",
        "tlit": "āyātuhu",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآيَاتِنَا",
        "answer": "in Our Signs",
        "pcklId": "330",
        "tlit": "biāyātinā",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآيَاتِنَا",
        "answer": "of Our Verses",
        "pcklId": "331",
        "tlit": "biāyātinā",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَاتِهِ",
        "answer": "His Signs",
        "pcklId": "332",
        "tlit": "āyātihi",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَاتِهِ",
        "answer": "His Signs",
        "pcklId": "333",
        "tlit": "āyātihi",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَاتِنَا",
        "answer": "Our Verses",
        "pcklId": "334",
        "tlit": "āyātinā",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَاتُهُ",
        "answer": "its verses",
        "pcklId": "335",
        "tlit": "āyātuhu",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَاتِنَا",
        "answer": "Our Signs",
        "pcklId": "336",
        "tlit": "āyātinā",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبَارَكَ",
        "answer": "and He blessed",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "wabāraka",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَبْشِرُوا",
        "answer": "but receive the glad tidings",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "wa-abshirū",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَشَرٌ",
        "answer": "a man",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "basharun",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَشِيرًا",
        "answer": "A giver of glad tidings",
        "pcklId": "109",
        "tlit": "bashīran",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَبْصَارُهُمْ",
        "answer": "and their sight",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "wa-abṣāruhum",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَبْصَارُكُمْ",
        "answer": "your sight",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "abṣārukum",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَصِيرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Seer",
        "pcklId": "105",
        "tlit": "baṣīrun",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَاطِلُ",
        "answer": "the falsehood",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "l-bāṭilu",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "119",
        "tlit": "baʿdi",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعِيدٍ",
        "answer": "far",
        "pcklId": "223",
        "tlit": "baʿīdin",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعِيدٍ",
        "answer": "far",
        "pcklId": "224",
        "tlit": "baʿīdin",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَبَيَّنَ",
        "answer": "becomes clear",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "yatabayyana",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَ",
        "answer": "(was) before them",
        "pcklId": "247",
        "tlit": "bayna",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَكَ",
        "answer": "between you",
        "pcklId": "248",
        "tlit": "baynaka",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبَيْنَهُ",
        "answer": "and between him",
        "pcklId": "249",
        "tlit": "wabaynahu",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَهُمْ",
        "answer": "between them",
        "pcklId": "250",
        "tlit": "baynahum",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنِنَا",
        "answer": "and between us",
        "pcklId": "315",
        "tlit": "bayninā",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبَيْنِكَ",
        "answer": "and between you",
        "pcklId": "316",
        "tlit": "wabaynika",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنِ",
        "answer": "from before them",
        "pcklId": "317",
        "tlit": "bayni",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنِ",
        "answer": "before it",
        "pcklId": "318",
        "tlit": "bayni",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَحْتَ",
        "answer": "under",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "taḥta",
        "frequency": "51",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "ثَمَرَاتٍ",
        "answer": "fruits",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "thamarātin",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَثْوًى",
        "answer": "(is) an abode",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "mathwan",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَجْحَدُونَ",
        "answer": "deny",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "yajḥadūna",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَجْحَدُونَ",
        "answer": "reject",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "yajḥadūna",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَنَجْزِيَنَّهُمْ",
        "answer": "and surely We will recompense them",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "walanajziyannahum",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَزَاءُ",
        "answer": "(is the) recompense",
        "pcklId": "102",
        "tlit": "jazāu",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَزَاءً",
        "answer": "(as) recompense",
        "pcklId": "103",
        "tlit": "jazāan",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَجْعَلُونَ",
        "answer": "and you set up",
        "pcklId": "263",
        "tlit": "watajʿalūna",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَعَلَ",
        "answer": "And He placed",
        "pcklId": "264",
        "tlit": "wajaʿala",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَجْعَلْهُمَا",
        "answer": "(so) we may put them",
        "pcklId": "265",
        "tlit": "najʿalhumā",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَعَلْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "We (had) made it",
        "pcklId": "266",
        "tlit": "jaʿalnāhu",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجُلُودُهُمْ",
        "answer": "and their skins",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "wajulūduhum",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِجُلُودِهِمْ",
        "answer": "to their skins",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "lijulūdihim",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "جُلُودُكُمْ",
        "answer": "your skins",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "julūdukum",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِجَانِبِهِ",
        "answer": "and distances himself",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "bijānibihi",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجِنِّ",
        "answer": "the jinn",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "l-jini",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجِنِّ",
        "answer": "the jinn",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "l-jini",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْجَنَّةِ",
        "answer": "of Paradise",
        "pcklId": "169",
        "tlit": "bil-janati",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَتْهُمُ",
        "answer": "came to them",
        "pcklId": "228",
        "tlit": "jāathumu",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءُوهَا",
        "answer": "they come to it",
        "pcklId": "229",
        "tlit": "jāūhā",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَهُمْ",
        "answer": "it comes to them",
        "pcklId": "230",
        "tlit": "jāahum",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاسْتَحَبُّوا",
        "answer": "but they preferred",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "fa-is'taḥabbū",
        "frequency": "95",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "حِجَابٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a screen",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "ḥijābun",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَحْزَنُوا",
        "answer": "grieve",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "taḥzanū",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحْسَنُ",
        "answer": "(is) better",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "aḥsanu",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحْسَنُ",
        "answer": "(is) better",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "aḥsanu",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَلْحُسْنَىٰ",
        "answer": "(will be) the best",
        "pcklId": "102",
        "tlit": "lalḥus'nā",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَسَنَةُ",
        "answer": "the good (deed)",
        "pcklId": "138",
        "tlit": "l-ḥasanatu",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحْشَرُ",
        "answer": "will be gathered",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "yuḥ'sharu",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَظٍّ",
        "answer": "(of) fortune",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "ḥaẓẓin",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَحِفْظًا",
        "answer": "and (to) guard",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "waḥif'ẓan",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَحَقَّ",
        "answer": "and (is) justified",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "waḥaqqa",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَقِّ",
        "answer": "[the] right",
        "pcklId": "236",
        "tlit": "l-ḥaqi",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَقُّ",
        "answer": "(is) the truth",
        "pcklId": "237",
        "tlit": "l-ḥaqu",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَكِيمٍ",
        "answer": "(the) All-Wise",
        "pcklId": "198",
        "tlit": "ḥakīmin",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَمِيدٍ",
        "answer": "(the) Praiseworthy",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "ḥamīdin",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَحْمِلُ",
        "answer": "bears",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "taḥmilu",
        "frequency": "64",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَمِيمٌ",
        "answer": "intimate",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "ḥamīmun",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُحِيطٌ",
        "answer": "encompassing",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "muḥīṭun",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَحِيصٍ",
        "answer": "place of escape",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "maḥīṣin",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحْيَاهَا",
        "answer": "gives it life",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "aḥyāhā",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَيَاةِ",
        "answer": "the life",
        "pcklId": "156",
        "tlit": "l-ḥayati",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَيَاةِ",
        "answer": "the life",
        "pcklId": "157",
        "tlit": "l-ḥayati",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَمُحْيِي",
        "answer": "(is) surely the Giver of life",
        "pcklId": "182",
        "tlit": "lamuḥ'yī",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَخْرُجُ",
        "answer": "comes out",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "takhruju",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخْزَىٰ",
        "answer": "(is) more disgracing",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "akhzā",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخِزْيِ",
        "answer": "(of) disgrace",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "l-khiz'yi",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَاسِرِينَ",
        "answer": "the losers",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "l-khāsirīna",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَاسِرِينَ",
        "answer": "losers",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "khāsirīna",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَاشِعَةً",
        "answer": "barren",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "khāshiʿatan",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَخْفَوْنَ",
        "answer": "hidden",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yakhfawna",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخُلْدِ",
        "answer": "(of) the eternity",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "l-khul'di",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاخْتُلِفَ",
        "answer": "but disputes arose",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "fa-ukh'tulifa",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلْفِهِمْ",
        "answer": "behind them",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "khalfihim",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلْفَهُمْ",
        "answer": "(was) behind them",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "khalfahum",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلْفِهِ",
        "answer": "behind it",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "khalfihi",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَقَ",
        "answer": "created",
        "pcklId": "123",
        "tlit": "khalaqa",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَقَهُمْ",
        "answer": "created them",
        "pcklId": "124",
        "tlit": "khalaqahum",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَقَكُمْ",
        "answer": "created you",
        "pcklId": "125",
        "tlit": "khalaqakum",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَقَهُنَّ",
        "answer": "created them",
        "pcklId": "126",
        "tlit": "khalaqahunna",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَتْ",
        "answer": "(that have) passed away",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "khalat",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَخَافُوا",
        "answer": "fear",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "takhāfū",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرٌ",
        "answer": "better",
        "pcklId": "177",
        "tlit": "khayrun",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَيْرِ",
        "answer": "(for) the good",
        "pcklId": "178",
        "tlit": "l-khayri",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُخَانٌ",
        "answer": "smoke",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "dukhānun",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَدْعُونَا",
        "answer": "you call us",
        "pcklId": "138",
        "tlit": "tadʿūnā",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَعَا",
        "answer": "invites",
        "pcklId": "139",
        "tlit": "daʿā",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَدْعُونَ",
        "answer": "invoking",
        "pcklId": "140",
        "tlit": "yadʿūna",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَدَّعُونَ",
        "answer": "you ask",
        "pcklId": "171",
        "tlit": "taddaʿūna",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُعَاءِ",
        "answer": "praying",
        "pcklId": "191",
        "tlit": "duʿāi",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُعَاءٍ",
        "answer": "(of) supplication",
        "pcklId": "192",
        "tlit": "duʿāin",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "ادْفَعْ",
        "answer": "Repel",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "id'faʿ",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدُّنْيَا",
        "answer": "[the world]",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "l-dun'yā",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدُّنْيَا",
        "answer": "(of) the world",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "l-dun'yā",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدُّنْيَا",
        "answer": "(of) the world",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "l-dun'yā",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَارُ",
        "answer": "(is the) home",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "dāru",
        "frequency": "55",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالذِّكْرِ",
        "answer": "in the Reminder",
        "pcklId": "251",
        "tlit": "bil-dhik'ri",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِنُذِيقَهُمْ",
        "answer": "that We may make them taste",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "linudhīqahum",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَلَنُذِيقَنَّ",
        "answer": "But surely We will cause to taste",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "falanudhīqanna",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَذَقْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "We let him taste",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "adhaqnāhu",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَنُذِيقَنَّهُمْ",
        "answer": "and We will surely make them taste",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "walanudhīqannahum",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرَوْا",
        "answer": "they see",
        "pcklId": "193",
        "tlit": "yaraw",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرَى",
        "answer": "see",
        "pcklId": "194",
        "tlit": "tarā",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرَأَيْتُمْ",
        "answer": "You see ",
        "pcklId": "195",
        "tlit": "ara-aytum",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرِنَا",
        "answer": "Show us",
        "pcklId": "306",
        "tlit": "arinā",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَنُرِيهِمْ",
        "answer": "Soon We will show them",
        "pcklId": "307",
        "tlit": "sanurīhim",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّ",
        "answer": "(is the) Lord",
        "pcklId": "741",
        "tlit": "rabbu",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّنَا",
        "answer": "our Lord",
        "pcklId": "742",
        "tlit": "rabbunā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِرَبِّكُمْ",
        "answer": "about your Lord",
        "pcklId": "743",
        "tlit": "birabbikum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّنَا",
        "answer": "Our Lord",
        "pcklId": "744",
        "tlit": "rabbanā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّنَا",
        "answer": "Our Lord",
        "pcklId": "745",
        "tlit": "rabbunā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "746",
        "tlit": "rabbika",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "747",
        "tlit": "rabbaka",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "748",
        "tlit": "rabbika",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّكَ",
        "answer": "(is) your Lord",
        "pcklId": "749",
        "tlit": "rabbuka",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّي",
        "answer": "my Lord",
        "pcklId": "750",
        "tlit": "rabbī",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِرَبِّكَ",
        "answer": "concerning your Lord",
        "pcklId": "751",
        "tlit": "birabbika",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِمْ",
        "answer": "(with) their Lord",
        "pcklId": "752",
        "tlit": "rabbihim",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْبَعَةِ",
        "answer": "four",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "arbaʿati",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَبَتْ",
        "answer": "and grows",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "warabat",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُرْجَعُونَ",
        "answer": "you will be returned",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "tur'jaʿūna",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "رُجِعْتُ",
        "answer": "I am returned",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "rujiʿ'tu",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّحْمَٰنِ",
        "answer": "the Most Gracious",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "tlit": "l-raḥmāni",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحْمَةً",
        "answer": "mercy",
        "pcklId": "201",
        "tlit": "raḥmatan",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّحِيمِ",
        "answer": "the Most Merciful",
        "pcklId": "308",
        "tlit": "l-raḥīmi",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحِيمٍ",
        "answer": "(the) Most Merciful",
        "pcklId": "309",
        "tlit": "raḥīmin",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُرَدُّ",
        "answer": "is referred",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "yuraddu",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْدَاكُمْ",
        "answer": "It has ruined you",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ardākum",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُرْسِلْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you have been sent",
        "pcklId": "100",
        "tlit": "ur'sil'tum",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَرْسَلْنَا",
        "answer": "So We sent",
        "pcklId": "101",
        "tlit": "fa-arsalnā",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرُّسُلُ",
        "answer": "the Messengers",
        "pcklId": "390",
        "tlit": "l-rusulu",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلرُّسُلِ",
        "answer": "to the Messengers",
        "pcklId": "391",
        "tlit": "lilrrusuli",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَوَاسِيَ",
        "answer": "firmly-set mountains",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "rawāsiya",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "رِيحًا",
        "answer": "a wind",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "rīḥan",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُرِيبٍ",
        "answer": "disquieting",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "murībin",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "الزَّكَاةَ",
        "answer": "the zakah",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "l-zakata",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَزَيَّنَّا",
        "answer": "And We adorned",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "wazayyannā",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَزَيَّنُوا",
        "answer": "(who) made fair-seeming",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "fazayyanū",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلسَّائِلِينَ",
        "answer": "for those who ask",
        "pcklId": "119",
        "tlit": "lilssāilīna",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْأَمُونَ",
        "answer": "tire",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yasamūna",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْأَمُ",
        "answer": "get tired",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yasamu",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُسَبِّحُونَ",
        "answer": "glorify",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "yusabbiḥūna",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبْعَ",
        "answer": "(as) seven",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "sabʿa",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبَقَتْ",
        "answer": "(that) preceded",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "sabaqat",
        "frequency": "37",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَسْتَتِرُونَ",
        "answer": "covering yourselves",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "tastatirūna",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَسْجُدُوا",
        "answer": "prostrate",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "tasjudū",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاسْجُدُوا",
        "answer": "but prostrate",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "wa-us'judū",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَسْفَلِينَ",
        "answer": "the lowest",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "l-asfalīna",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُسْلِمِينَ",
        "answer": "those who submit",
        "pcklId": "130",
        "tlit": "l-mus'limīna",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْمَعُونَ",
        "answer": "hear",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "yasmaʿūna",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَسْمَعُوا",
        "answer": "listen",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "tasmaʿū",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَمْعُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their hearing",
        "pcklId": "126",
        "tlit": "samʿuhum",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَمْعُكُمْ",
        "answer": "your hearing",
        "pcklId": "127",
        "tlit": "samʿukum",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمِيعُ",
        "answer": "(is) the All-Hearer",
        "pcklId": "169",
        "tlit": "l-samīʿu",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاءِ",
        "answer": "the heaven",
        "pcklId": "265",
        "tlit": "l-samāi",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَمَاوَاتٍ",
        "answer": "heavens",
        "pcklId": "266",
        "tlit": "samāwātin",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَمَاءٍ",
        "answer": "heaven",
        "pcklId": "267",
        "tlit": "samāin",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاءَ",
        "answer": "the heaven",
        "pcklId": "268",
        "tlit": "l-samāa",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَسَاءَ",
        "answer": "does evil",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "asāa",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَسْوَأَ",
        "answer": "(the) worst",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "aswa-a",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّيِّئَةُ",
        "answer": "the evil (deed)",
        "pcklId": "125",
        "tlit": "l-sayi-atu",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّاعَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Hour",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "l-sāʿati",
        "frequency": "49",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّاعَةَ",
        "answer": "the Hour",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "l-sāʿata",
        "frequency": "49",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتَوَىٰ",
        "answer": "He directed (Himself)",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "is'tawā",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَسْتَوِي",
        "answer": "(are) equal",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "tastawī",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَوَاءً",
        "answer": "equal",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "sawāan",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَشَدُّ",
        "answer": "(is) mightier",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "ashaddu",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَشَدُّ",
        "answer": "(is) Mightier",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "ashaddu",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَدِيدًا",
        "answer": "severe",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "shadīdan",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّرُّ",
        "answer": "the evil",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "l-sharu",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّرُّ",
        "answer": "the evil",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "l-sharu",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "شُرَكَائِي",
        "answer": "My partners",
        "pcklId": "113",
        "tlit": "shurakāī",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْمُشْرِكِينَ",
        "answer": "to the polytheists",
        "pcklId": "155",
        "tlit": "lil'mush'rikīna",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّيْطَانِ",
        "answer": "the Shaitaan",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "l-shayṭāni",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَشِفَاءٌ",
        "answer": "and a healing",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "washifāon",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "شِقَاقٍ",
        "answer": "opposition",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "shiqāqin",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَكٍّ",
        "answer": "doubt",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "shakkin",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالشَّمْسُ",
        "answer": "and the sun",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "wal-shamsu",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلشَّمْسِ",
        "answer": "to the sun",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "lilshamsi",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَهِدَ",
        "answer": "(will) testify",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "shahida",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَهِدْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you testify",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "shahidttum",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشْهَدَ",
        "answer": "testify",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "yashhada",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَهِيدٍ",
        "answer": "witness",
        "pcklId": "112",
        "tlit": "shahīdin",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَهِيدٌ",
        "answer": "a Witness",
        "pcklId": "132",
        "tlit": "shahīdun",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَشْتَهِي",
        "answer": "desire",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "tashtahī",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَاءَ",
        "answer": "(had) willed",
        "pcklId": "183",
        "tlit": "shāa",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "شِئْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you will",
        "pcklId": "184",
        "tlit": "shi'tum",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing",
        "pcklId": "457",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing",
        "pcklId": "458",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "things",
        "pcklId": "459",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "things",
        "pcklId": "460",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَصْبَحْتُمْ",
        "answer": "and you have become",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "fa-aṣbaḥtum",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِمَصَابِيحَ",
        "answer": "with lamps",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "bimaṣābīḥa",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَصْبِرُوا",
        "answer": "they endure",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "yaṣbirū",
        "frequency": "103",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَبَرُوا",
        "answer": "(are) patient",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "ṣabarū",
        "frequency": "103",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَرْصَرًا",
        "answer": "furious",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ṣarṣaran",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَاعِقَةً",
        "answer": "(of) a thunderbolt",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "ṣāʿiqatan",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَاعِقَةِ",
        "answer": "(the) thunderbolt",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "ṣāʿiqati",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَاعِقَةُ",
        "answer": "a thunderbolt",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "ṣāʿiqatu",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَالِحًا",
        "answer": "righteous (deeds)",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "ṣāliḥan",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَالِحًا",
        "answer": "righteous deeds",
        "pcklId": "92",
        "tlit": "ṣāliḥan",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّالِحَاتِ",
        "answer": "righteous deeds",
        "pcklId": "153",
        "tlit": "l-ṣāliḥāti",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضَرَّاءَ",
        "answer": "an adversity",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "ḍarrāa",
        "frequency": "74",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَضَلَّ",
        "answer": "And lost",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "waḍalla",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَضَلَّانَا",
        "answer": "misled us",
        "pcklId": "107",
        "tlit": "aḍallānā",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَضَلُّ",
        "answer": "(is) more astray",
        "pcklId": "124",
        "tlit": "aḍallu",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَوْعًا",
        "answer": "willingly",
        "pcklId": "125",
        "tlit": "ṭawʿan",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَائِعِينَ",
        "answer": "willingly",
        "pcklId": "126",
        "tlit": "ṭāiʿīna",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِظَلَّامٍ",
        "answer": "unjust",
        "pcklId": "132",
        "tlit": "biẓallāmin",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَنَنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you assumed",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "ẓanantum",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَنَنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you assumed",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "ẓanantum",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَظَنُّوا",
        "answer": "and they (will) be certain",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "waẓannū",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَظُنُّ",
        "answer": "I think",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "aẓunnu",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَنُّكُمُ",
        "answer": "(was) your assumption",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "ẓannukumu",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْبُدُوا",
        "answer": "worship",
        "pcklId": "104",
        "tlit": "taʿbudū",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْبُدُونَ",
        "answer": "worship",
        "pcklId": "105",
        "tlit": "taʿbudūna",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْعَبِيدِ",
        "answer": "to His slaves",
        "pcklId": "238",
        "tlit": "lil'ʿabīdi",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَعْتِبُوا",
        "answer": "they ask for favor",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yastaʿtibū",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُعْتَبِينَ",
        "answer": "those who receive favor",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "l-muʿ'tabīna",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَأَعْجَمِيٌّ",
        "answer": "(Is it) a foreign (language)",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "āʿ'jamiyyun",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْجَمِيًّا",
        "answer": "(in) a foreign (language)",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "aʿjamiyyan",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَدَاوَةٌ",
        "answer": "(was) enmity",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "ʿadāwatun",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْدَاءُ",
        "answer": "(the) enemies",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "aʿdāu",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْدَاءِ",
        "answer": "(of the) enemies",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "aʿdāi",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابَ",
        "answer": "(the) punishment",
        "pcklId": "283",
        "tlit": "ʿadhāba",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَعَذَابُ",
        "answer": "And surely, (the) punishment",
        "pcklId": "284",
        "tlit": "walaʿadhābu",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَذَابِ",
        "answer": "(of) the punishment",
        "pcklId": "285",
        "tlit": "l-ʿadhābi",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابًا",
        "answer": "a punishment",
        "pcklId": "286",
        "tlit": "ʿadhāban",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابٍ",
        "answer": "a punishment",
        "pcklId": "287",
        "tlit": "ʿadhābin",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَرَبِيًّا",
        "answer": "(in) Arabic",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "ʿarabiyyan",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَرَبِيٌّ",
        "answer": "and an Arab",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "waʿarabiyyun",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَعْرَضَ",
        "answer": "but turn away",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "fa-aʿraḍa",
        "frequency": "79",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْرَضُوا",
        "answer": "they turn away",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "aʿraḍū",
        "frequency": "79",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْرَضَ",
        "answer": "he turns away ",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "aʿraḍa",
        "frequency": "79",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَرِيضٍ",
        "answer": "lengthy",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "ʿarīḍin",
        "frequency": "79",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَزِيزِ",
        "answer": "(of) the All-Mighty",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "l-ʿazīzi",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَزِيزٌ",
        "answer": "mighty",
        "pcklId": "94",
        "tlit": "ʿazīzun",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَظِيمٍ",
        "answer": "great",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "ʿaẓīmin",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِقَابٍ",
        "answer": "(of) penalty",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "ʿiqābin",
        "frequency": "80",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "(who) know",
        "pcklId": "310",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "know",
        "pcklId": "311",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَالَمِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the worlds",
        "pcklId": "537",
        "tlit": "l-ʿālamīna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِلْمُ",
        "answer": "(the) knowledge",
        "pcklId": "638",
        "tlit": "ʿil'mu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِعِلْمِهِ",
        "answer": "with His knowledge",
        "pcklId": "639",
        "tlit": "biʿil'mihi",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَلِيمِ",
        "answer": "the All-Knower",
        "pcklId": "745",
        "tlit": "l-ʿalīmi",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَلِيمُ",
        "answer": "the All-Knower",
        "pcklId": "746",
        "tlit": "l-ʿalīmu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاعْمَلْ",
        "answer": "So work",
        "pcklId": "214",
        "tlit": "fa-iʿ'mal",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَمِلُوا",
        "answer": "and do",
        "pcklId": "215",
        "tlit": "waʿamilū",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "do",
        "pcklId": "216",
        "tlit": "yaʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "you do",
        "pcklId": "217",
        "tlit": "taʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "do",
        "pcklId": "218",
        "tlit": "yaʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَمِلَ",
        "answer": "and does",
        "pcklId": "219",
        "tlit": "waʿamila",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "اعْمَلُوا",
        "answer": "Do",
        "pcklId": "220",
        "tlit": "iʿ'malū",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "you do",
        "pcklId": "221",
        "tlit": "taʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَمِلَ",
        "answer": "does",
        "pcklId": "222",
        "tlit": "ʿamila",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَمِلُوا",
        "answer": "they did",
        "pcklId": "223",
        "tlit": "ʿamilū",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَامِلُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) working",
        "pcklId": "358",
        "tlit": "ʿāmilūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَمَىٰ",
        "answer": "[the] blindness",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "l-ʿamā",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَمًى",
        "answer": "blindness",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "ʿaman",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَ",
        "answer": "(are) near",
        "pcklId": "127",
        "tlit": "ʿinda",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَهُ",
        "answer": "with Him",
        "pcklId": "128",
        "tlit": "ʿindahu",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدِ",
        "answer": "from",
        "pcklId": "192",
        "tlit": "ʿindi",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَادٍ",
        "answer": "(of) Aad",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "ʿādin",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَادٌ",
        "answer": "Aad",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "ʿādun",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاسْتَعِذْ",
        "answer": "then seek refuge",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "fa-is'taʿidh",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاسْتَغْفِرُوهُ",
        "answer": "and ask His forgiveness",
        "pcklId": "92",
        "tlit": "wa-is'taghfirūhu",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَفُورٍ",
        "answer": "(the) Oft-Forgiving",
        "pcklId": "164",
        "tlit": "ghafūrin",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَغْفِرَةٍ",
        "answer": "(of) forgiveness",
        "pcklId": "221",
        "tlit": "maghfiratin",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَغْلِبُونَ",
        "answer": "overcome",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "taghlibūna",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَلِيظٍ",
        "answer": "severe",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "ghalīẓin",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَيْرُ",
        "answer": "never ending",
        "pcklId": "131",
        "tlit": "ghayru",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِغَيْرِ",
        "answer": "without",
        "pcklId": "132",
        "tlit": "bighayri",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "فُصِّلَتْ",
        "answer": "are detailed",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "fuṣṣilat",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "فُصِّلَتْ",
        "answer": "are explained in detail",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "fuṣṣilat",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَوْقِهَا",
        "answer": "above it",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "fawqihā",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلِهِمْ",
        "answer": "before them",
        "pcklId": "196",
        "tlit": "qablihim",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلِكَ",
        "answer": "before you",
        "pcklId": "197",
        "tlit": "qablika",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلُ",
        "answer": "before",
        "pcklId": "198",
        "tlit": "qablu",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَدَّرَ",
        "answer": "and determined",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "waqaddara",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَدِيرٌ",
        "answer": "All-Powerful",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "qadīrun",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقْدِيرُ",
        "answer": "(is the) Decree",
        "pcklId": "126",
        "tlit": "taqdīru",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَقْدَامِنَا",
        "answer": "our feet",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "aqdāminā",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُرْآنًا",
        "answer": "a Quran",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "qur'ānan",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقُرْآنِ",
        "answer": "Quran",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "l-qur'āni",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُرْآنًا",
        "answer": "a Quran",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "qur'ānan",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُرَنَاءَ",
        "answer": "companions",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "quranāa",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَقَضَاهُنَّ",
        "answer": "Then He completed them",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "faqaḍāhunna",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَقُضِيَ",
        "answer": "surely, would have been settled",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "laquḍiya",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلُوبُنَا",
        "answer": "Our hearts",
        "pcklId": "126",
        "tlit": "qulūbunā",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْقَمَرُ",
        "answer": "and the moon",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "wal-qamaru",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْقَمَرِ",
        "answer": "to the moon",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "lil'qamari",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَنُوطٌ",
        "answer": "(and) despairs",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "qanūṭun",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَقْوَاتَهَا",
        "answer": "its sustenance",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "aqwātahā",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالُوا",
        "answer": "And they say",
        "pcklId": "1398",
        "tlit": "waqālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "1399",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "1400",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَقَالَ",
        "answer": "and He said",
        "pcklId": "1401",
        "tlit": "faqāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَتَا",
        "answer": "They both said",
        "pcklId": "1402",
        "tlit": "qālatā",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَقُلْ",
        "answer": "then say",
        "pcklId": "1403",
        "tlit": "faqul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They said",
        "pcklId": "1404",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالُوا",
        "answer": "and they said",
        "pcklId": "1405",
        "tlit": "waqālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالُوا",
        "answer": "And they will say",
        "pcklId": "1406",
        "tlit": "waqālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They will say",
        "pcklId": "1407",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالَ",
        "answer": "And said",
        "pcklId": "1408",
        "tlit": "waqāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالَ",
        "answer": "And (will) say",
        "pcklId": "1409",
        "tlit": "waqāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "say",
        "pcklId": "1410",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالَ",
        "answer": "and says",
        "pcklId": "1411",
        "tlit": "waqāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُقَالُ",
        "answer": "is said",
        "pcklId": "1412",
        "tlit": "yuqālu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "قِيلَ",
        "answer": "was said",
        "pcklId": "1413",
        "tlit": "qīla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَقَالُوا",
        "answer": "they (would have) said",
        "pcklId": "1414",
        "tlit": "laqālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "1415",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They will say",
        "pcklId": "1416",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيَقُولَنَّ",
        "answer": "he will surely say",
        "pcklId": "1417",
        "tlit": "layaqūlanna",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "1418",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوْلُ",
        "answer": "the Word",
        "pcklId": "1695",
        "tlit": "l-qawlu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْلًا",
        "answer": "(in) speech",
        "pcklId": "1696",
        "tlit": "qawlan",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاسْتَقِيمُوا",
        "answer": "so take a Straight Path",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "fa-is'taqīmū",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتَقَامُوا",
        "answer": "stand firm ",
        "pcklId": "92",
        "tlit": "is'taqāmū",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِقَوْمٍ",
        "answer": "for a people",
        "pcklId": "423",
        "tlit": "liqawmin",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقِيَامَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) Resurrection",
        "pcklId": "548",
        "tlit": "l-qiyāmati",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَائِمَةً",
        "answer": "(will be) established",
        "pcklId": "602",
        "tlit": "qāimatan",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُوَّةً",
        "answer": "(in) strength",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "quwwatan",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُوَّةً",
        "answer": "(in) strength",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "quwwatan",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَيَّضْنَا",
        "answer": "And We have destined",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "waqayyaḍnā",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاسْتَكْبَرُوا",
        "answer": "they were arrogant",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "fa-is'takbarū",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتَكْبَرُوا",
        "answer": "they are arrogant",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "is'takbarū",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "كِتَابٌ",
        "answer": "A Book",
        "pcklId": "261",
        "tlit": "kitābun",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَكِتَابٌ",
        "answer": "(is) surely a Book",
        "pcklId": "262",
        "tlit": "lakitābun",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابَ",
        "answer": "the Book",
        "pcklId": "263",
        "tlit": "l-kitāba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَكْثَرُهُمْ",
        "answer": "most of them",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "aktharuhum",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَثِيرًا",
        "answer": "much",
        "pcklId": "123",
        "tlit": "kathīran",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَرْهًا",
        "answer": "unwillingly",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "karhan",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكْسِبُونَ",
        "answer": "earn",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "yaksibūna",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَتَكْفُرُونَ",
        "answer": "[surely] disbelieve",
        "pcklId": "228",
        "tlit": "latakfurūna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieve",
        "pcklId": "229",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieve",
        "pcklId": "230",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieve",
        "pcklId": "231",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieve",
        "pcklId": "232",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieved",
        "pcklId": "233",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you disbelieve",
        "pcklId": "234",
        "tlit": "kafartum",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَافِرُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "490",
        "tlit": "kāfirūna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَافِرُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "491",
        "tlit": "kāfirūna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكْفِ",
        "answer": "sufficient",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "yakfi",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلِّ",
        "answer": "each",
        "pcklId": "288",
        "tlit": "kulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلَّ",
        "answer": "every",
        "pcklId": "289",
        "tlit": "kulla",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلِّ",
        "answer": "every",
        "pcklId": "290",
        "tlit": "kulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلِّ",
        "answer": "all",
        "pcklId": "291",
        "tlit": "kulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِكُلِّ",
        "answer": "(is) of all",
        "pcklId": "292",
        "tlit": "bikulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَلِمَةٌ",
        "answer": "(for) a word",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "kalimatun",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَكْمَامِهَا",
        "answer": "their coverings",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "akmāmihā",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَكِنَّةٍ",
        "answer": "coverings",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "akinnatin",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَانُوا",
        "answer": "But they used to",
        "pcklId": "1134",
        "tlit": "wakānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they used to",
        "pcklId": "1135",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَانُوا",
        "answer": "and used to",
        "pcklId": "1136",
        "tlit": "wakānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they used to",
        "pcklId": "1137",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you were",
        "pcklId": "1138",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "were",
        "pcklId": "1139",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they used to",
        "pcklId": "1140",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they used to",
        "pcklId": "1141",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيَكُونَا",
        "answer": "that they be",
        "pcklId": "1142",
        "tlit": "liyakūnā",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you were",
        "pcklId": "1143",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you",
        "pcklId": "1144",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they were",
        "pcklId": "1145",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "it is",
        "pcklId": "1146",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَكَانٍ",
        "answer": "a place",
        "pcklId": "1381",
        "tlit": "makānin",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُلْحِدُونَ",
        "answer": "distort",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yul'ḥidūna",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْغَوْا",
        "answer": "and make noise",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wal-ghaw",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُلَقَّاهَا",
        "answer": "it is granted",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "yulaqqāhā",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُلَقَّاهَا",
        "answer": "it is granted",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "yulaqqāhā",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُلْقَىٰ",
        "answer": "is cast",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "yul'qā",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِقَاءِ",
        "answer": "(the) meeting",
        "pcklId": "130",
        "tlit": "liqāi",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّيْلُ",
        "answer": "(are) the night",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "al-laylu",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّيْلِ",
        "answer": "by night",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "bi-al-layli",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِثْلُكُمْ",
        "answer": "like you",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "mith'lukum",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِثْلَ",
        "answer": "like",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "mith'la",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَرَّةٍ",
        "answer": "time",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "marratin",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِرْيَةٍ",
        "answer": "doubt",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "mir'yatin",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَسَّهُ",
        "answer": "touches him",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "massahu",
        "frequency": "61",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَسَّتْهُ",
        "answer": "(has) touched him",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "massathu",
        "frequency": "61",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَسَّهُ",
        "answer": "touches him",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "massahu",
        "frequency": "61",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَلَائِكَةً",
        "answer": "Angels",
        "pcklId": "180",
        "tlit": "malāikatan",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَلَائِكَةُ",
        "answer": "the Angels",
        "pcklId": "181",
        "tlit": "l-malāikatu",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَمْنُونٍ",
        "answer": "never ending",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "mamnūnin",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَوْتَىٰ",
        "answer": "(to) the dead",
        "pcklId": "158",
        "tlit": "l-mawtā",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَاءَ",
        "answer": "water",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "l-māa",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَأَىٰ",
        "answer": "and distances himself",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wanaā",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَلَنُنَبِّئَنَّ",
        "answer": "But We will surely inform",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "falanunabbi-anna",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَجَّيْنَا",
        "answer": "And We saved",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "wanajjaynā",
        "frequency": "84",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَحِسَاتٍ",
        "answer": "(of) misfortune",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "naḥisātin",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْدَادًا",
        "answer": "rivals",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "andādan",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنَادَوْنَ",
        "answer": "are being called",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "yunādawna",
        "frequency": "53",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنَادِيهِمْ",
        "answer": "He will call them",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "yunādīhim",
        "frequency": "53",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْذَرْتُكُمْ",
        "answer": "I have warned you",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "andhartukum",
        "frequency": "130",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَذِيرًا",
        "answer": "and a warner",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "wanadhīran",
        "frequency": "130",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْزَغَنَّكَ",
        "answer": "whisper comes to you",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yanzaghannaka",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَزْغٌ",
        "answer": "an evil suggestion",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "nazghun",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَأَنْزَلَ",
        "answer": "surely, He (would have) sent down",
        "pcklId": "228",
        "tlit": "la-anzala",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْزَلْنَا",
        "answer": "We send down",
        "pcklId": "229",
        "tlit": "anzalnā",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَتَنَزَّلُ",
        "answer": "will descend",
        "pcklId": "255",
        "tlit": "tatanazzalu",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُزُلًا",
        "answer": "A hospitable gift",
        "pcklId": "265",
        "tlit": "nuzulan",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَنْزِيلٌ",
        "answer": "A revelation",
        "pcklId": "277",
        "tlit": "tanzīlun",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَنْزِيلٌ",
        "answer": "A Revelation",
        "pcklId": "278",
        "tlit": "tanzīlun",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنْصَرُونَ",
        "answer": "will not be helped",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "yunṣarūna",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْطَقَنَا",
        "answer": "Allah made us speak",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "anṭaqanā",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْطَقَ",
        "answer": "makes speak",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "anṭaqa",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْعَمْنَا",
        "answer": "We bestow favor",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "anʿamnā",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسُكُمْ",
        "answer": "your souls",
        "pcklId": "253",
        "tlit": "anfusukum",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَلِنَفْسِهِ",
        "answer": "then it is for his soul",
        "pcklId": "254",
        "tlit": "falinafsihi",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسِهِمْ",
        "answer": "themselves",
        "pcklId": "255",
        "tlit": "anfusihim",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالنَّهَارُ",
        "answer": "and the day",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "wal-nahāru",
        "frequency": "113",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالنَّهَارِ",
        "answer": "and day",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "wal-nahāri",
        "frequency": "113",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّارِ",
        "answer": "the Fire",
        "pcklId": "109",
        "tlit": "l-nāri",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَالنَّارُ",
        "answer": "the Fire",
        "pcklId": "110",
        "tlit": "fal-nāru",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّارُ",
        "answer": "the Fire",
        "pcklId": "111",
        "tlit": "l-nāru",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّارِ",
        "answer": "the Fire",
        "pcklId": "112",
        "tlit": "l-nāri",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَهَدَيْنَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "We guided them",
        "pcklId": "118",
        "tlit": "fahadaynāhum",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْهُدَىٰ",
        "answer": "the guidance",
        "pcklId": "270",
        "tlit": "l-hudā",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "هُدًى",
        "answer": "a guidance",
        "pcklId": "271",
        "tlit": "hudan",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "اهْتَزَّتْ",
        "answer": "it is stirred (to life)",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ih'tazzat",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْهُونِ",
        "answer": "humiliating",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "l-hūni",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاحِدٌ",
        "answer": "One",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "wāḥidun",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُوحَىٰ",
        "answer": "it is revealed",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "yūḥā",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَوْحَىٰ",
        "answer": "and He revealed",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "wa-awḥā",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُوزَعُونَ",
        "answer": "will be assembled in rows",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yūzaʿūna",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَضَعُ",
        "answer": "gives birth",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "taḍaʿu",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُوعَدُونَ",
        "answer": "promised",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "tūʿadūna",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقْرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) deafness",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "waqrun",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقْرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) deafness",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "waqrun",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَّقُونَ",
        "answer": "fear (Allah)",
        "pcklId": "160",
        "tlit": "yattaqūna",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوْلِيَاؤُكُمْ",
        "answer": "(are) your protectors",
        "pcklId": "213",
        "tlit": "awliyāukum",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِيٌّ",
        "answer": "(was) a friend",
        "pcklId": "214",
        "tlit": "waliyyun",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَيَئُوسٌ",
        "answer": "then he gives up hope",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "fayaūsun",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيْدِيهِمْ",
        "answer": "from before them",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "aydīhim",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيْدِيهِمْ",
        "answer": "(was) before them",
        "pcklId": "92",
        "tlit": "aydīhim",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَدَيْهِ",
        "answer": "before it",
        "pcklId": "93",
        "tlit": "yadayhi",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمَيْنِ",
        "answer": "two periods",
        "pcklId": "229",
        "tlit": "yawmayni",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيَّامٍ",
        "answer": "periods",
        "pcklId": "230",
        "tlit": "ayyāmin",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمَيْنِ",
        "answer": "two periods",
        "pcklId": "231",
        "tlit": "yawmayni",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيَّامٍ",
        "answer": "(the) days",
        "pcklId": "232",
        "tlit": "ayyāmin",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمَ",
        "answer": "(on the) Day",
        "pcklId": "233",
        "tlit": "yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَوْمَ",
        "answer": "And (the) Day",
        "pcklId": "234",
        "tlit": "wayawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَوْمَ",
        "answer": "And (the) Day",
        "pcklId": "380",
        "tlit": "wayawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "41",
        "ayah": "19"
    }
]; 
export default words;